<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Japan</string>
    <string name="totoro_long_desc">My Neighbor Totoro (となりのトトロ) is a 1988 Japanese animated fantasy film written and directed by Hayao Miyazaki and produced by Studio Ghibli. The film – which stars the voice actors Noriko Hidaka, Chika Sakamoto, and Hitoshi Takagi – tells the story of the two young daughters (Satsuki and Mei) of a professor and their interactions with friendly wood spirits in postwar rural Japan. The film won the Animage Anime Grand Prix prize and the Mainichi Film Award and Kinema Junpo Award for Best Film in 1988. It also received the Special Award at the Blue Ribbon Awards in the same year.</string>
    <string name="mononoke_long_desc">Princess Mononoke (もののけ姫) is a 1997 Japanese epic historical fantasy anime film written and directed by Hayao Miyazaki. It was animated by Studio Ghibli and produced by Toshio Suzuki. The film stars the voices of Yōji Matsuda, Yuriko Ishida, Yūko Tanaka, Kaoru Kobayashi, Masahiko Nishimura, Tsunehiko Kamijo, Akihiro Miwa, Mitsuko Mori and Hisaya Morishige.\n\nPrincess Mononoke is set in the late Muromachi period (approximately 1336 to 1573) of Japan with fantasy elements. The story follows the young Emishi prince Ashitaka\'s involvement in a struggle between the gods of a forest and the humans who consume its resources. The term "Mononoke" (物の怪 or もののけ) is not a name, but a Japanese word for a spirit or monster. Unlike Ghibli\'s earlier films, Mononoke has a darker and more violent setting and tone.\n\nThe film was released in Japan on July 12, 1997, and in the United States on October 29, 1999. It was a critical and commercial blockbuster, becoming the highest-grossing film in Japan of 1997, and the highest-grossing there of all time until Titanic was released later that year. It was dubbed into English and distributed in North America by Miramax, and despite a poor box office performance there, it sold well on DVD and video, greatly increasing Ghibli\'s popularity and influence outside Japan.</string>
    <string name="chihiro_long_desc">Spirited Away (千と千尋の神隠し) is a 2001 Japanese anime fantasy film written and directed by Hayao Miyazaki and produced by Studio Ghibli. The film stars Rumi Hiiragi, Miyu Irino, Mari Natsuki, Takeshi Naito, Yasuko Sawaguchi, Tsunehiko Kamijō, Takehiko Ono, and Bunta Sugawara, and tells the story of Chihiro Ogino (Hiiragi), a sullen ten-year-old girl who, while moving to a new neighborhood, enters the spirit world. After her parents are transformed into pigs by the witch Yubaba (Natsuki), Chihiro takes a job working in Yubaba\'s bathhouse to find a way to free herself and her parents and return to the human world.</string>
    <string name="samurai_long_desc">Seven Samurai (七人の侍) is a 1954 Japanese epic historical drama adventure film co-written, edited, and directed by Akira Kurosawa. The story takes place in 1586 during the Sengoku Period of Japanese history. It follows the story of a village of farmers that hire seven ronin (masterless samurai) to combat bandits who will return after the harvest to steal their crops.\n\n Since its release, Seven Samurai has consistently ranked highly in critics\' greatest films lists, such as the BFI\'s Sight and Sound and Rotten Tomatoes polls. It has remained highly influential, often seen as a masterpiece and one of the most "remade, reworked, referenced" films in cinema.</string>
    <string name="jed_url">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.umibouzu.jed</string>
    <string name="akebi_url">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.craxic.akebifree</string>
    <string name="kanji_url">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=jp.rodriguez.kanjisenpai.android</string>
    <string name="trad_url">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.translate</string>
</resources>
